威尔 · 森塔斯: 好吧，我们来谈谈
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: All right,
so let's talk about what
这个背包叫做，因为我想我们都同意。
this backpack is called,
because I think we can all agree.
顺便说一下，自从我们赢了以后，事情已经发生了变化。
This is an ever by the way,
things have changed since we won.
这位女士的名字背包被炸飞了
This lady's name backpack
has been blowing up
有人给我买了一件 t 恤，背面有个背包。
somebody's got me a T shirt with
a backpack on the back of it.
我认为这构成了巨大的爆炸。
I count that as constituting
blowing up huge.
确实有一件 t 恤。
There is one t shirt, exactly.
但是，现在有一个博客贴出了最受欢迎的关闭博客帖子。
But also, there is now a blog post
the most popular blog posts on closure.
由《卫报》和《纽约时报》撰稿。
Outlet written by the Guardian and
New York Times.
工程经理纽约时报你来到了困难的部分，酷。
Engineering manager New York Times
you came to hard part's, cool.
我一直不明白什么叫了结直到我想到了这个,
I never understood closure
until I thought about this way,
通过这种方式，他提到了那个背包14次。
learnt about this way, in which he
referred to the backpack, 14 times.
没错，14 / 15毫米宽，没错。
Yeah, exactly, wow,
14/15 millimeter wide, exactly.
这就是现实变得多么真实。
That's how real is becoming.
我们正在游说规格制造商。
We're lobbying the spec makers.
演讲者2: (笑)威尔 · 森塔斯: 显然不是但是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And obviously not but
我想你们都没听说过
I don't think any of you heard of, and
当然还有人听说过，不过有个好听的名字。
certainly another heard of it,
but there is a fancy name for it.
开发人员对它有一个通俗的称呼。
There is a colloquial name
used by developers for it.
我只是不喜欢存在的原因是我认为它是模糊和不精确的。
I just don't love the reason being
is I think it's vague and imprecise.
它指的是两者的整体概念，他们也称之为背包。
It refers to both of the overall concept,
and they call the backpack this as well.
所以这些是，让我把它说得更好。
So these are, let me put that better.
它们指的是导致背包存在和
They refer to the thing that results
in the backpack existing and
他们把背包叫做同样的伞形术语。
they call the backpack all
this same umbrella term.
我认为这是一个有点模糊和混乱。
I think that is a bit vague and confusing.
所以我要给我们的背包起一些好听的名字
So I'm gonna give us some fancy names for
the backpack and
那为什么我们有背包。
then why we have the backpack.
那么名字呢，我之前已经告诉过你们了
So first name, well I already told
you earlier on that people pool
他们的局部记忆有时变化的环境。
their local memory sometimes
the variable environment.
作为一个才华横溢的开发者，我认为谁有一本精彩的书，实际上我
As a brilliant I think developer out there
who's a wonderful book actually which I
强烈推荐朋友喜欢一个聪明，但
highly recommend for
friends known as like a smart but
不像一本书，让我做笔记。
isn't like a book like let me take notes.
这就是所谓的如果海明威写 Javascript。
This is called
If Hemingway Wrote Javascript.
是的，我认为这是一本完美的礼品书，我实际上买了十本。
Yeah, I think it's a perfect gift book,
I bought ten copies actually.
它没有暗示太多关于-无论如何，我得到了他们为
It doesn't suggest much about the- anyway,
I got them for
史密斯代码的人我觉得这是最糟糕的圣诞礼物了,
Code Smith people, I think, it's gotta
be the worst Christmas gift ever,
没错，你会得到一本《当海明威写作时》。
right, you're getting a copy
of When Hemingway Wrote.
所以如果我读海明威写的由 Gaga Angus Crow 编写的 JavaScript,
So if I read, Hemingway wrote
JavaScript by Gaga Angus Crow,
他非常喜欢这个，他称之为基本上他只需要一小段代码
a big fan of it, he calls this is
basically he takes little snippets of code
就像斐波那契序列一样，并以著名作家的风格写在网站上。
like Fibonacci sequence and writes them in
the site in the style of famous writers.
所以海明威的很简洁，纳博科夫的我不知道，我没有读过,
So Hemingway's is very terse,
Nabokov's I don't know, I didn't read it,
但我不知道该说什么。
but I don't know what to say.
但是，威尔 · 森坦斯: 他把这个叫做背包,
But so,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: He calls this backpack,
他称之为结案陈词。
he calls it the closed over.
也就是说，我们关闭了这里的数据，关闭了变量环境。
That is to say we close a lid on this data
here, closed over variable environment.
也就是说，我们把可变的环境,
That is to say,
we take the variable environment,
盖上盖子，然后拔出来。
kinda close a lid on it, and pull it out.
好的，他称之为曲线，结束
Okay, so he calls it the curve,
closed over
变量环境代码，不是个坏名字。
variable environment code,
not a bad name for it.
我想我喜欢它，这里有一个我很喜欢的名字。
I guess I like it,
now here's a name I quite like for it.
我想这就是我所说的，如果你可以说你保证会成为一名高年级学生
I think this is the one that I said if
you can say you're guaranteed a senior
开发人员的工作。
developer job.
显然我得收回那句话。
I have to take that back obviously.
所以听到这个名字，这是很好的,
So hear the name, that it is nice,
这表明了我们对。
it shows a depth to understanding.
所以这里的数据是持久的。
So this data here is persistent.
对，它一直存在，不像常规的数据被删除,
Right, it sticks around, it's not like
the regular data that gets deleted,
这是持久的。
it's persistent.
这是数据，好吧，d 代表数据。
It's data, okay, d for data.
它被引用了，被链接了
It's referenced, it's linked
由 scope 属性引用，好的。
referenced by a scope property, okay.
什么是范围？
What is scope?
范围是任何编程语言的规则。
Scope is the rules in any
programming language.
对于任何给定的代码行，我有什么数据可用？
For at any given line of code,
what data do I have available to me?
所以如果我每天都在这条线上如果我在这条线上,
So if I'm in this line every day as
this is it, if I'm in this line,
我可以通过某种方式访问这些数据，还有这些数据。
somehow I have access to this data,
and this data.
范围是什么数据和规则是什么的花哨词汇
Scope is the fancy word for
what data and what are the rules for
但是我们假设如果我运行一个函数。
but we assume that if I
run a function like outer.
如果我们没有发现内部数据和 global 有联系，为什么？
in global that if we don't find data
inside out to be connected to global, why?
这不像是由开发人员决定的编程语言所固有的
That's not like inherent in a programming
language that was decided by the developer
当他们决定给定语言的范围规则时。
of the language, when they're deciding the
rules of scope for that given language.
在我的运行中的任何给定行对我可用的数据的规则
The rules of what data is available to
me at any given line in my running of
我的密码。
my code.
你可以想象一种语言里面没有可用的新数据
You can imagine a language says
no new data available inside that
功能，就是这个。
function, that's it.
呼叫所有的地区语言
Beep every regional language and
作用域规则是只保护函数本身内部的数据。
the scoping rule would be protecting
the data only inside the function itself.
你不能访问那些函数数据。
You don't have access
to that functions data.
也就是说，语言是范围规则。
That would be that language is scope rule.
这是 JavaScript 语言有一个非常特殊的作用域规则。
This the language of JavaScript
has a very particular scope rule.
它的范围规则是。
Its scope rule is.
所谓的词法范围或静态范围。
What's called lexical or static scoping.
也就是说，我保存我的功能的地方
That is to say that
where I save my function
决定了其余的生命，决定了其功能的生命。
determines for the rest of that life,
for the life of that function.
无论它以何种新标签运行,
Whenever it gets run under
whatever new label it gets,
当这个函数运行时，它能访问哪些数据。
what data it will have access
to when that function runs.
不是我经营的地方。
Is not where I run it.
这就是所谓的动态范围。
That would be called dynamic scoping.
它会根据我运行函数的位置而变化。
It changes depending on
where I run the function.
如果我要动态地调用语言，我会运行我的新函数和
If I were to dynamically scope language,
I'd run my new functioning and
我会直接向下看全球，不会发现计数器就是它。
I'd look straight down to global,
wouldn't find counter that was it.
是一种静态的或者词汇范围限定的语言。
JavaScript is a static or
lexically scoped language.
词汇是指页面上的物理位置。
Lexical means the physical
positioning on the page.
我物理上把它放在外部的运行中。
I physically position this
inside the running of outer.
是一种静态的词汇范围语言。
Is a lexical statically scope language.
这意味着即使我返回我的函数，并且
That means that even if I
returned my function out, and
理论上所有的数据都应该被删除。
theoretically all this data
should have been deleted.
不，因为我有这个词汇范围语言的基本规则。
Nope, because I have this fundamental
rule of lexically scoped language.
我得把幕后的数据都拿来
I'm gonna have to grab all that
data behind the scenes and
放在背包上。
put it out on the backpack.
这样，当我运行函数时，我仍然拥有上次作用域时的所有数据。
Such that when I run the function, I still
have all the data from when I last scope.
不是因为我回到了之前的执行环境。
Not because I go back into
the earlier execution context, uh-uh.
我要回到外层去。
I'm going back up into outer.
我不需要这样做---- 我从 incrementCounter 函数出现的时候提取了数据
I didn't have to, I pulled the data from
when the function incrementCounter was
我的词汇范围属性。
born out with me on my
lexical scope property.
在幕后，我把数据拿出来
Behind the scenes I
pulled the data out and
把它和我的新功能连在一起。
left it attached to now my new function.
这是一种词汇范围的语言。
It's a lexically scoped language.
持久的词法或静态范围引用数据。
Persistent lexically or
static scope reference data.
所以特殊类型的作用域，即词法作用域，具有静态作用域规则
So special type of scope, the lexical
scope, with static scoping rule
也就是说，我们把函数诞生时的数据带来了。
which means we literally bring the data
with us from when the function was born.
因为我们的规则是我的函数保存在哪里决定
Because our rule is where my
function was saved determines
我能访问哪些数据，什么时候最终运行，不管它在哪里。
what data I have access to, when it's
eventually run, wherever that may be.
这里是持久化的词法静态范围引用数据。
And there it is persistent lexical
static scope reference data.
你们可以看到这就是为什么我叫它背包，看看这个美丽的名字。
And you can see that's why I call it the
back pack, look at that beautiful name.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 但是在工业界，他们倾向于使用
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But
in industry they tend to use
Kayla 之前给我们的口语词。
the colloquial term that
Kayla gave us earlier.
也就是说，把数据放到函数的闭包中。
Which is they say,
put the data in the function's closure.
我对这个术语的看法是，它的整体概念很酷
My problem with that term is a cool
the overall concept, the notion of
他们称之为结束，然后他们称之为背包结束。
lexical scoping and they call that closure
and then they call the backpack closure.
这是由于 JavaScript 是一个词典范围的结果
It's the backpack as a result of
JavaScript being a lexically scoped
语言，一个把数据和函数一起带到函数所到之处的语言,
language, one that brings the data with
the function wherever that function goes,
藏在望远镜里，藏在背包里。
hidden on the scope property,
hidden on the backpack.
这意味着如果你在房间里保存一个函数，另一个函数。
Meaning that if you save a function
inside the room another function.
当它退出的时候，这些都应该被删除，不。
When it exits,
that should all be deleted, nope.
但是把这些数据放在背包里所以当我们运行这个功能时,
But bringing that data with us on
the backpack so when we run that function,
它仍然可以访问背包里的持久数据。
it still has access to that
persistent data from its backpack.
我们走吧，我们还没有完全结束。
There we go people,
we're not quite done yet.
[声音]在这一点上我们应该做点什么，以防这会引起任何新的问题。
[SOUND] Let's do thumbs at that point in
case this is raise any new questions.
你把我弄糊涂了，不要到处看。
You lost me clear clarification,
no looking around.
托德，我看到你在四处张望。
Todd, I saw you looking around.
是好的澄清。
Is okay good clarifications.
彼得有一个。
Peter has one.
彼得，请继续。
Peter, go ahead please.
Peter: 如果你定义了一个新的变量作为我的新函数,
&gt;&gt; Peter: If you defined a new variable
that you defined as my new function,
它也能拿到它的背包吗？
would it also get its backpack?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 好吧，那么
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Okay, so
我们可以说一些有趣的附加事情。
there is a couple of interesting
bonus things we can say around that.
你是说如果我们说彼得
So you're saying if we
said let's say Peter =
我的新功能你是这个意思吗？
my new Function,
is that what you're saying?
是啊那就是说 peter 现在是个新标签了
Yeah, so that would just be
peter is now a new label for
同样的功能，同样的背包。
this same function with the same backpack.
是的 彼得: 它仍然可以访问所有的-
Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Peter: It still gets access to all the-
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，当然。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, absolutely.
因为那只是现在彼得是一个新的标签
Cuz that's just now
peter is a new label for
同样的功能，所有的东西都附着在上面。
this same function with all
the stuff attached to it.
这是字面上附加到功能。
This is literally
attached to the function.
Mynewfunction 现在是所有这一切的标签。
myNewFunction is the label for
all of this together now.
函数代码运行，我的意思是，想想这个。
Function code to run, I mean,
just think about this.
它被标记为一个可以创建的函数代码，所以是内存。
It's labeled for a function code
to run that can create, so memory.
但是它也有自己的永久记忆。
But it's also got its own
permanent memory attached to it.
这真是太不寻常了。
That is kind of extraordinary.
还有一件事我想补充一下
Yeah.
There's one other thing I do want to add
还是长话短说吧。
actually, keep it short.
但是，如果我从相同的外部执行返回，自由函数。
But, if I returned out from the same
outer execution, free functions.
顺便说一句如果你需要归还那个东西,
Which by the way,
if you need to return that one things,
如何从学生合同中返回三个函数？
how can I return out three
functions from a student contracts?
是的，丹。
Yeah, Dan.
Dan: 在函数数组中。
&gt;&gt; Dan: In array of array of functions.
方法的函数或对象数组,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Array of function or
object for the methods yeah,
它们都与同一个背包相连。
they would all be linking
to the same backpack.
所以他们都可以使用那个共享背包。
And so they'd all have access
to that share backpack.
挺酷的。
That's kind of cool.
但这还不是我们要去的地方。
But that's not where we're going yet.
我还以为我们要养彼得呢，这是最后一块了。
I thought we were going to raise
Peter is this final piece here.
我们在这里看到了这一切。
So we saw all this here.
我称之为背包紧密在变化的环境持久词汇,
What I call the backpack close over
variable environment persistent lexically,
范围或标准东科特，参考数据，缓存，背包或封闭。
scoped or standard eastcote, reference
data, cache, backpack or closure.
实时数据的背包或关闭附加到增量计数器上
The backpack or closure of live data
is attached to increment counter
通过被称为作用域的隐藏属性。
via the hidden property known as scope.
即使在返回这个内部函数时，它仍然持久存在。
Which persists, even when this
inner function is returned out.
我们随身携带所有的数据，然后从函数的背面提取出来。
We grab all that data with us and
pull it out, on the back of the function.
所以当我们用这个函数的新标签时,
So as we we use that
function by its new label,
我们仍然可以访问所有的数据。
we still have access to all that data.
而且是永久的。
And it's permanent.
它不会消失。
It ain't going away.